If you have people in your life that will tell you the honest truth, really regard them and understand that the honest truth does not always have to be characterized as negative.
You do yourself a very real disservice when you consider somebody giving you insight with the intent of informing as someone being negative.
Don't get me wrong, there's always the people who are like always trying to undermine something, who are always trying to look for the holes and always trying to find, okay, wait, wait, wait, where's the negative part?
Like those people, yeah, you don't want that.
But anybody trying to save you time, energy, or disappointment is here for you.
And oftentimes when someone tells you an inconvenient truth, it can do all of those things.
And it's not about like, oh, well, they didn't say it nicely.
What other way is there to say it than just this is what it is?
So learn to receive that because it'll save you a whole lot of heartache.
Be careful of people who try to on those folks in order to just cheerlead to cheerlead because they really just trying to live vicariously through you because they're not really on their own shit.